Toggle navigation [The Startup Squad](https://www.thestartupsquad.com/)

* 0
    * No products in the cart.

Search 

Privacy Policy
==============

**Privacy Policy**

We are committed to protecting your private information. This Statement of Privacy applies to [www.thestartupsquad.com](https://www.thestartupsquad.com/) and The Harold Martin Company (“HMC”) and governs data collection and usage. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, unless otherwise noted, all references to The Harold Martin Company or HMC include [www.thestartupsquad.com](https://www.thestartupsquad.com/). The [www.thestartupsquad.com](https://www.thestartupsquad.com/) website (the “Site”) is a blog and ecommerce site. By using the HMC website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.

**Collection of your Personal Information**  
In order to better provide you with products and services offered on our Site, HMC may collect personally identifiable information, such as your Name, E-mail Address, Zip Code, State of Residence, Child Name, Child Age, Name of Child’s Business, and URL of Child’s Business.

If you purchase HMC’s products and services, we collect billing, shipping, and credit card information. This information is used to complete the purchase transaction, screen our orders for potential risk or fraud, and, when in line with the preferences you have shared with us, provide you with information or advertising relating to our products or services.

HMC may also collect anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your Age and Gender.

Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through HMC’s public message boards, this information may be collected and used by others.

We do not collect any personal information about you unless you voluntarily provide it to us. However, you may be required to provide certain personal information to us when you elect to use certain products or services available on the Site. These may include: (a) registering for an account or newsletter on our Site; (b) entering a sweepstakes or contest sponsored by us or one of our partners; (c) signing up for special offers from selected third parties; (d) sending us an email message; (e) submitting your credit card or other payment information when ordering and purchasing products and services on our Site. To wit, we will use your information for, but not limited to, communicating with you in relation to services and/or products you have requested from us. We also may gather additional personal or non-personal information in the future.

**Use of your Personal Information**  
HMC collects and uses your personal information to operate its website(s) and deliver the services you have requested.

HMC may also use your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from HMC and its affiliates.

**How you can access, change or suppress your Personal Information**  
If you would like to review, correct, update, suppress or delete personal information that you have provided to us, contact us at the address below.  In your request, please make clear what personal information you would like to have changed, whether you would like to have the personal information you have provided to us suppressed from our database, or otherwise let us know what limitations you would like to put on our use of the personal information you have provided us.  For your protection, we may only implement requests with respect to the personal information associated with the particular email address that you use to send us your request, and we may need to verify your identity before implementing your request.  We will try to comply with your request as soon as reasonably practicable.

Please note that we may need to retain certain information for recordkeeping purposes and/or to complete any transactions that you began prior to requesting such change or deletion.  There may also be residual information that will remain within our databases and other records and which will not be removed.

**Sharing Information with Third Parties**  
HMC does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties.

HMC may share data with trusted partners to help perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to HMC, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.

HMC may disclose your personal information, without notice, if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on HMC or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of HMC; and/or (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of HMC, or the public.

**Tracking User Behavior**  
HMC may keep track of the websites and pages our users visit within HMC, in order to determine what HMC services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within HMC to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.

**Automatically Collected Information**  
Information about your computer hardware and software may be automatically collected by HMC. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of HMC.

**Use of Cookies**  
HMC may use “cookies” to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize HMC pages, or register with HMC or its services, a cookie helps HMC to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same HMC website, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the HMC features that you customized.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the HMC services or websites you visit.

**Links**  
This website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information.

**Security of your Personal Information**  
HMC secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. HMC uses SSL Protocol for this purpose. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other websites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) protocol.

We strive to take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or alteration of your personal information. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, you acknowledge that: (a) there are security and privacy limitations inherent to the Internet which are beyond our control; and (b) security, integrity, and privacy of any and all information and data exchanged between you and us through this Site cannot be guaranteed.

**Children Under Thirteen**  
HMC is a general audience website and is not geared towards children. In order to protect the privacy of children, HMC does not knowingly collect information online from children under 13 without prior parental consent. HMC may collect personally identifiable information pertaining to children under the age of 13 from parents with parental consent such as: name, age, state of residence, zip code, name of business, URL of business, and user-generated content. HMC collects this information to ensure a child’s eligibility for a contest and as entry for such contest.

If you are under the age of thirteen, you must ask your parent or guardian for permission to use this website. If you are a parent and believe we have collected information from your child, please contact us using the information provided at the end of this Statement of Privacy so that we can work to delete it. If you are a parent and you have questions regarding our data collection practices, please contact us using the information provided at the end of this Statement of Privacy.

**International Visitors**  
HMC is hosted in the United States and is intended for visitors located within the United States. If you choose to use HMC from the European Union or other regions of the world with laws governing data collection and use that may differ from U.S. law, then please note that you are transferring your personally identifiable information outside of those regions to the United States for storage and processing, and by providing your personally identifiable information to HMC you consent to that transfer, storage, and processing.

**E-mail Communications**  
From time to time, HMC may contact you via email for the purpose of providing announcements, promotional offers, alerts, confirmations, surveys, and/or other general communication. In order to improve our Services, we may receive a notification when you open an email from HMC or click on a link therein.

If you would like to stop receiving marketing or promotional communications via email from HMC, you may opt out of such communications by clicking on the UNSUBSCRIBE button.

**External Data Storage Sites**  
We may store your data on servers provided by third party hosting vendors with whom we have contracted.

**Changes to this Statement**  
HMC reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your account, by placing a prominent notice on our site, and/or by updating any privacy information on this page. Your continued use of the Site and/or Services available through this Site after such modifications will constitute your: (a) acknowledgment of the modified Privacy Policy; and (b) agreement to abide and be bound by that Policy.

**Contact Information**  
HMC welcomes your questions or comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that HMC has not adhered to this Statement, please contact HMC at:

The Harold Martin Company  
221 Main Street, #749  
Los Altos, California 94023

Email Address:  
\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_\_

Effective as of June 04, 2018

© 2024 The Startup Squad
